Accomplished professional at an early stage startup that successfully raised a \$13 million series-A. Total of 9 years of experience, including 3 years in the tech industry. Graduated from an intense 12-week software development bootcamp, totaling 40 hours per week. An efficient and motivated work ethic, with the drive to continuously learn, and grow as a teammate.

# Junda Jay Chen

Pittsburgh | 412-716-7452 | jundachen10@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/jundachen | github.com/jundachen10

# Experience

# **Software Engineer: Contract**

2023

Looking For Group, LLC

Pittsburgh, PA

- Leading weekly stand-up meetings and managing projects using Kanban boards.
- Developing a .NET app that distributes login credentials using SignalR and WPF.

**Entrepreneur** 2022 – 2023 Owner Co Founder Pittsburgh, PA

- Graduated from a 12 week full-stack developer bootcamp at 40+ hours per week.
- Founded a film and marketing company that earned \$50,000 annual run rate.
- Co Founded a venture with another experienced engineer and scraped 300,000 JSON data points stored in a Mongo database.

#### **Lead Customer Success Manager and Growth Marketer**

2019 - 2022

Gridwise Mobile App

Pittsburgh, PA

- Hybrid role at an early stage startup.
- Influenced securing a \$3.3M and \$12.7M series A funding as an early hire.
- Pioneered a customer support function that scaled with 5x user growth. Developed key performance indicators and established robust systems, rituals, and processes.
- Facilitated monthly strategic meetings as a growth marketer with the CEO and VP of Growth.
- Collaborated across functions to drive user growth from 25,000 to 300,000 at a high-growth mobile app startup.
- Expanded coverage on a main product by 700% by building a team of 10 QA contractors to support it.
- Launched a knowledge base by curating support articles, resulting in a monthly viewership of 3,000.
- Increased customer support productivity by 90% by automating repeat tasks using Zendesk triggers and Zapier integrations.
- Introduced Zendesk systems that resolved 600 monthly tickets with a 98% satisfaction rate.
- Launched the company YouTube channel from zero to 2,700 subs within a single year.
- Tripled Facebook groups membership through use of A/B tests optimizing post performance and engagement.
- Improved marketing ROI by 200% partnered with the VP of Marketing to identify top creatives using statistical methods like T-tests.
- Reduced B2B client churn by 20% partnered with Director of Sales in improving click-through rates using Mixpanel and Everflow attribution.
- Developed content management calendars that resulted in a 2 season podcast and over 60 videos.
- Led on-site user interviews which resulted in 3 testimonial videos.
- Completed projects within an Agile framework across 30+ development sprints.

# Research Technician

University of Pittsburgh

2010 - 2018

Pittsburgh, PA

- Co-authored 3 papers in the Journal of Neuroscience and IEEE.
- Mentored 3 undergraduate students over 6 months on research methods.
- Achieved liver cell transplant under GMP process at the Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh.
- · Budgeted for daily laboratory expenditures and negotiated with vendors to maximize budget.

# **Projects**

#### Portfolio | Next.js, React, JavaScript, Vercel, HTML, CSS, Git

• Built with Next.js, deployed to Vercel, has dark mode, and fetches real-time GitHub stats.

#### **This Resume** | Github Actions

• Wrote a custom GitHub Actions automation that seamlessly deploys a PDF when changes are pushed to the repo.

#### **Buzzfeed** | C#, SQL, SQLite, DBeaver

• Buzzfeed like game, uses SQL to fetch quizzes from a remote database.

#### **Technical Skills**

**Dev Tools**: Docker, VS Code, Visual Studio **Languages**: JavaScript, C#, SQL, HTML, CSS **Frameworks**: React, Next.js, jQuery, Git, Agile

Product: Jira, Asana, Notion, Zapier, GSuite, Airtable, Slite

**Design**: Figma, Final Cut Pro, Davinci Resolve **Analytics**: Mixpanel, Segment, Google, Youtube

Martech: HubSpot, Salesforce, SendGrid, Mailchimp, Ahrefs Customer: Zendesk, Zendesk Explore, Confluence, Salesforce

### Soft Skills

Earned \$21,000 in revenue and 100,000 subscribers on YouTube.

Founded a film company in Pittsburgh. Ranked top 8% League of Legends.

Classically trained pianist.

#### Education

The Pennsylvania State University	University Park, PA
•	Offiversity Fark, FA
Bachelor of Science in Biology	2010
University of Pittsburgh	Pittsburgh, PA
Completed Masters Coursework in Public Health Genetics	2017
Academy Pittsburgh	Pittsburgh, PA
Diploma in Software Development	2023